MINJOO YUN UX DESIGNER

minjoodesign.com hi@minjoodesign.com +1-650-206-3130 It's incredibly important to start with an accurate picture of who I am designing for and what problems I am trying to solve. I love to design & iterate through tests and researches.

EXPERIENCE

Google | Verily

UI/UX Designer (Contract)

South San Francisco, CA 2018 - Present I've worked on various portfolio of projects on Health Platforms, from patient-facing disease management solutions to health system-facing population management tools.

I collaborated with cross-functional teams to create a new registry UX, packaging and instructional manual for hardware devices, and software solutions for patients and clinicians.

KarFarm

UI Designer

Sunnyvale, CA 2017 - 2018 Collaborating with PM, engineers, and marketing manager, I redesigned the user experience for mobile app onboarding flow and designed the marketing website. Also, I provided assets and UX specifications for product excellence.

Clincase

UX Design Intern

Berlin, Germany 2016 - 2016 As a UX design intern, I designed end to end feature work in collaboration with cross-functional partners. I supported the migration of the patient reported ourcome (PRO) instrument from paper to electronic format for Clincase EPRO 1.0 I created low-fidelity and hi-fidelity prototypes of end-to-end experiences for desktop, tablet, and mobile devices. Linkewise, I produced and developed relevant, effective visual design, such as icons, illustrations, etc.

BlueStacks UX Design Intern

Campbell, CA 2015 - 2016 I conducted user research and analyzed collected data for user interface acceptability and designed visual assets to contribute to BlueStacks TV—a platform that empowers global gamers to stream apps from thier computer to Twitch.

EDUCATION

San Jose State University | Bachelor of Fine Arts in Graphic Design

San Jose, CA June 2015 - May 2018

General Assembly | Front-end Development

San Francisco, CA December 2017 - March 2018

SKILLS

Competency

Product Design Interaction Design Visual Design Rapid Prototyping Design Research

Code/Interaction

| HTML, CSS, JavaScript |
|------------------------------|
| (learning), React JS |
| (learning), jQuery, ProtoPie |
| Figma, Invision, Framer |

Graphic

Sketch, Photoshop,
Illustrator, InDesign,
AfterEffect